(Leonard:)Nice little bot you've got here.
(Kripke:)I'm aware.
(Leonard:)What's this do, spin?
(Kripke:)Yep. At 3400 rpm.
(Kripke:)It can cut through steel
like it was rubber.
(Leonard:)Neat.
(Leonard:)Good work.
Sheldon, we've gotta call this off.
(Sheldon:)No, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)For years, merciless thugs like Kripke have
made my life a series of painful noogies...
(Sheldon:)...and humiliating wedgies
and the insensitively named Indian burns.
- Well, that stops now.
- Sheldon, we don't have a chance.
(Raj:)The only improvement
you were able to make...
(Raj:)...was to put fresh batteries
in the remote.
(Sheldon:)What you fail to realize is Kripke suffers
from a fatal flaw:
(Sheldon:)Overconfidence from his robot's
massive size and its overwhelming power.
(Raj:)That's not overconfidence.
That's observation.